Scott J. Bayreder

147 Lavaca Loop Hutto, TX 78634 sbayreder@gmail.com (303) 229-0182

SUMMARY

A motivated sales professional with 5+ years experience with Mattress Firm. Capable of communicating effectively and professionally with teams. Who is a strong leader with various years of experience. Reliable, confident worker with a commitment to complete all assigned tasks and exceed expectations. Has been awarded several times for meeting and exceeding expectations, both personally and professionally.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Microsoft Office proficient
- Professional Communication skills
- Leadership and development skills

EDUCATION

Arapahoe Community College: Denver, Colorado

May 2012 – December 2013

March 2014 - Present

General Studies

• Major: Biology

• Minor: Business Management

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mattress Firm: Houston, Texas

Store Manager

- Oversees a book of business of over \$1.1 million dollars
- Trained and developed 6 store managers, an area manger and 6 interns
- Worked with vendor reps on merchandising tasks
- Have implemented several merchandising changes that have improved store profitability
- Awarded ACE Award and the Savage Award

Petsmart: Parker. Colorado

Pet care manager

- Oversees all living animals in the building
- Trains and develops pet care staff
- Responsible for opening and closing the store
- Handles P&L for department
- Manager of the Year 2013

Mountain West Chiropractic: Las Vegas, Nevada

February 2007 – April 2012

Chiropractic Assistant

- New patient exams, X-rays, and patient therapies.
- Responsible for helping patients choose mattresses that were better suited to their afflictions.
- Responsible for merchandising therapy products for the office.
- Awarded Chiropractic Assistant Excellence Award for 2008, 2009 and 2011

Leslie's Pool Supply: Henderson, Nevada

February 2005- February 2007

Assistant Store Manager

- Created and designed plan-o- gram for store merchandise
- Responsible for creating sales promotions to move product or generate new business
- Grew profitability from Tier 2 store (under \$500k) to an Eagle 1 store (over \$1.5 mil) in first year
- Awarded highest annual growth award